Kugisaki! Don't let that blood touch you!
You think I don't know that?!
Run away,
with your backs to me.
Kugisaki, can you go any faster?
No way!
I've got your back.
Thanks.
Huh?
Huh?!
What speed...
While carrying someone, too.
Tsk... They'll get away.
Well, no matter.
Okay, we're out of range now.
Well done. You have my compliments.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm kidding. Thank you.
It took the shortest route
and got ahead of us?
Itado—
Kugisaki!
You don't need to worry.
My younger brother's blood doesn't
have the same quality as mine.
And even mine won't kill you
unless your entire body's bathed in it.
Though it will hurt like hell.
This is where our technique starts.
Rot Technique: Decay.
Huh?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
My blood, and my brothers' blood,
Episode 24: Accomplices
is absorbed through wounds and membranes,
and then, once any of us
brothers activates the technique,
it begins to rot you away
from the point of incursion.
I'd give that young man
about fifteen minutes.
Ten minutes max for you, young lady.
By morning, nothing but bones will remain.
If it's a technique,
we just need to make them release it!
So it is poisonous.
The result is essentially a poison,
but our technique is purely "decomposition."
I've finished revealing our technique.
Now they'll actually die even faster.
So, what will you do now?
Elder Brother, these sorcerers
didn't amount to much.
At the beginning of the Meiji Era,
there was a girl with a unique trait that
allowed her to bear a cursed spirit's child.
She conceived a child
with no recollection of how,
and the criticism she endured from
her parents and relatives was extreme.
She fled with the corpse
of her baby in her arms,
ending up at a temple run
by a certain jujutsu sorcerer.
However, that was where her luck ran out.
Kamo Noritoshi.
Among all of jujutsu
sorcery's cultural legacy,
he's remembered as
the most vile of sorcerers
and a disgrace to the three major clans.
His intellectual curiosity
was captivated by the possibility of a
child born of a human and a cursed spirit.
Nine times, he impregnated her.
Nine times, he aborted her.
All records of how he did it
and what happened to her
afterward were destroyed.
The Cursed Wombs:
Death Paintings One through Three
became cursed objects powerful enough
to be classified as special-grade.
Perhaps the origin of that power
was the mother's resentment,
or perhaps...
I have no memories of a mother.
Humans and sorcerers...
It's not that I hold any
special grudge against them.
For 150 years,
we remained sealed away with nothing
but each others' existence to rely on.
We'll side with the cursed spirits.
Are you sure?
They seemed shady, Elder Brother.
The future those cursed spirits painted
is more convenient for us.
That's all there is to it.
Forget about owing them
for our manifestation.
Now listen, brothers.
Eso, you live for Kechizu.
Kechizu, you live for me.
And I'll live for you, Eso.
We three are one.
I live for my brothers.
If it is what my brothers desire,
I will give my life to grant it for them.
If the suffering is too great,
would you like me to end you right away?
A technique that guarantees
victory once it hits...
You two are strong.
Too bad for you, though.
That makes me the worst match for you!
Straw Doll Technique: Resonance!
Let's play a game of chicken!
You don't like pain, do you?
Then start crying and
release your technique.
A technique to turn the curse on the user?
A game of chicken...
So unless I release our technique,
this will continue?
Straw Doll Technique: Resonance.
It's a technique that deals damage
to the target's main body
by driving cursed energy through an effigy
and a lost portion of the target.
The technique's range is broad,
and the effect varies
with the difference in strength between
us and the value of the lost portion.
As far as Straw Doll Technique is concerned,
blood isn't very valuable.
But Resonance uses the link to its target.
And their blood that's inside me now
is strongly linking us and
their rot technique together!
It's a nice surprise that it worked
on the younger brother, too.
If I'm going to die here anyway,
then I'll keep hammering
Resonance into them!
That's quite intense,
but no matter how many times she
does it, it won't end our lives.
As long as we hold out,
you'll be the ones to die!
Not to mention,
while Decay is active, the pain
and poison will keep you from mov—
How are you able to move that well?
Resonance!
Itadori is the vessel
for Ryomen Sukuna,
the King of Curses and Deadly Poisons.
So he has resistance to all forms of poison.
The result is essentially a poison,
but our technique is purely "decomposition."
He's probably feeling pain
from the decomposition,
but the resulting poison doesn't affect him.
And if it's just pain...
Itadori Yuji...
won't stop!
Kechizu!
Shut up already!
Resonance!
That's nothing!
He switched!
With the woman close to death,
putting her against my brother,
who's closer to death!
Does she think she can stop
my movement forever?!
Woman!
Do I release the technique or not?
I can't go and save my brother like this!
I can't unleash Wing King
while Decay is active.
But does that woman have enough
strength left to kill my brother?
Even with her interference,
this man won't be able
to kill me before she dies,
so I cannot release the technique!
B-Brother!
We three are one.
I was already releasing it before I even knew it.
Wing King!
What was that black light just now?
I know I reinforced my arm with
cursed energy before taking his punch!
But the next thing I knew, my whole arm
and shoulder had been blown away.
Ahh, younger brother!
Don't die, my brother!
Elder Brother!
I haven't shown you this one yet, have I?
Hairpin.
Don't worry.
I'll be sending your older
brother to join you soon.
Kechizu...
We three are one.
I'm sorry, Elder Brother.
Even though I was with him...
Why isn't this thing vanishing?
Is it still alive?
No!
It's not a cursed spirit!
It has a physical body!
Watch it!
Christ.
S-Sawamura-san?!
Speed up.
Hit the brakes and you're dead.
Both you and him.
Got it?
Don't follow me, jujutsu sorcerer.
Once I heal my wounds,
I'll make sure to kill these two,
especially that woman.
I'm sorry, Kechizu...
I wasn't able to mourn you.
But I will get revenge for—
What is that woman doing?
Kugisaki!
Don't rush me!
Straw Doll Technique:
Resonance!
Once they land a Black Flash,
sorcerers temporarily enter
a state athletes call "the zone."
Damn it!
It wasn't a technique to
turn the curse on the user?!
Sorry.
That hurt.
Geto, the stock certificate.
What's the matter, Choso?
Hurry up.
Hey! Don't break the pieces!
My younger brothers died.
You can tell?
What's going on?
It's one thing if he was fully manifested,
but I find it hard to believe those two were
killed by a single finger of a cursed spirit.
Jeez, do we have any more?
Hold on.
Why aren't there spares?
And why did you break it?
We just received a report.
Eso and Kechizu were killed
Jeez.
by the first-years of Jujutsu High...
Itadori Yuji and his group.
The number you have dialed is—
I knew it! They're not answering!
Where did those brats go?!
Kugisaki, you okay?
Oh, yeah.
Though it might leave scars.
I wonder if those old guys are all right.
Their truck's gone, too.
The poison's...
Well, if we head home now,
I wonder if Shoko-san'll be awake.
And I wonder if she'll be sober...
What are you fidgeting for? It's creepy.
I was wondering if this was your first time
killing instead of exorcising.
What about you?
I did it once before...
No, I guess it isn't fair to call it once.
It was three people.
I think you're doing worse than me here.
To be blunt, this was nothing to me.
These things happen when you're a sorcerer.
I'm no Fushiguro,
but ultimately, there are only
so many people we can save.
There are only so many seats open in my life,
and I don't want to let my heart be swayed
by anyone who's not sitting in one of them.
Is that mean?
Of course, there are also people like you
who bring their own seat and sit down.
It might not mean much,
but we didn't have room to worry about
whether they were cursed spirits or curse users.
Even if they were human,
we don't have a technique to keep anyone
that strong restrained long-term.
You know that, right?
But he cried when he saw
his brother die before him.
I see.
I'm happy that you and I
were spared and are still alive.
It's a big relief.
But tears were shed over
the lives I ended tonight.
That's all.
I see.
In that case, we're accomplices.
F-Fushiguro?!
Oh, you're back.
I'm glad you're safe.
I-I was so scared!
I thought you were dead!
Thank goodness!
Could you lower your voices?
My head hurts.
Don't go to sleep with Sukuna's finger
in your hand. That's dangerous.
How do you know about the finger?
You have the energy to ask about that?
Nope.
Just contact Nitta-san for now.
We need to get it sealed at once.
Cursed spirits are approaching.
Should I eat it?
It's not leftovers.
We don't have a clear idea of
how many fingers you can handle.
So don't eat it.
But I will hand it over to you,
since you have the most energy.
I'll say this again, though. Don't eat it.
He thinks I have the intelligence of a dog.
We just said not to eat it!
Huh? Me?!
This guy seriously...
He hardly did any work this time, either!
The Sukuna within you will tell us where
the fingers are to try to regain his power.
Is Gojo-sensei just winging it?
You just now realized?
Hey! You three!
What have you three been doing?!
Oh, Nitta-san.
You wouldn't answer my calls!
She's lost it.
What's the big idea?!
Well, shall we go home?
Didn't you learn that communication,
consulting, and reporting are important?!
I'm hungry.
Are you listening to me?! Hey, you!
I wonder if there's a
Splendid Sushi around here.
Splendid Sushi's bullet train
was awesome, wasn't it?
Shut up.
Man, it wasn't just a cursed spirit with a finger.
When we analyzed the
corpses, what a surprise!
It was the manifestation of the other goods.
They each took out one special-grade!
This year's first-years
are the cream of the crop!
It must be my skill as an instructor.
I don't want any long chats
with you on my day off.
You're calling about arrangements
for the drinking party, right?
Well, find any candidates?
None.
Everyone's busy, even myself.
What now? Should I try
asking the students, too?
I'm a lightweight, so I don't mind
if the party's alcohol-free.
I'm counting on you to
keep reaching out to people.
Iori Utahime
We never know what might be
listening around Utahime, after all.
I don't want to think about one
of the students being the traitor.
This is such a pain.
Payment for: Gojo Satoru
Enter password to verify
Password
Confirm Payment
Well, I'll leave the rest to you, Mei-san.
Payment Complete
The payment has been sent.
Gojo Satoru
Don't talk about them
resonating with Itadori.
Are you certain about that?
Nearly positive. The case is over, though.
The only ones likely to notice
are us and Nitta-san.
Itadori...
and Sukuna's manifestation
was only the trigger.
The curse of Yasohachi Bridge could
have started killing at any moment.
Besides, he swallowed that
first finger to save me.
But there's no way he'd be
satisfied with just that.
So don't tell him.
I won't say anything.
Don't underestimate a lady's consideration.
It's your fault!
You took me in.
And now the severed parts
of my soul have awakened.
To save lots of people, was it?
Brat!
People are going to die because you live!
Hey... Don't say that to Fushiguro.
But what are you going to do when someone
you saved kills someone else in the future?
Don't you dare say it.
Mustard leaf.
What's wrong? Your movements
aren't as sharp today.
Did you get weaker?
Shut up!
I lost my edge after all that bed rest!
Anyway, did you hear about the first-years?
Yeah.
They took out three special-grades, right?
Salmon.
Then...
We can't fall behind, either.
Roe.
Yeah!
Hey! You were serious that time!
It wouldn't be good training
if I wasn't serious.
Kelp.
Even among sorcerers,
the rank of special-grade is a
position beyond the normal scope.
It's my belief that first-grades
are the ones who ought to lead other
sorcerers and the jujutsu world.
The danger, confidential information, and pay
that they deal with is nothing like
what those semi-first-grade and below do.
So with that in mind,
what did you just say?
Zen'in Maki,
Panda...
Fushiguro Megumi,
Kugisaki Nobara,
and my brother, Itadori Yuji.
These are the five that I,
by my name as Todo Aoi...
...and I, by my name as Mei Mei...
...recommend for first grade.
I think you're just buying way too much.
Half of that is yours, right?
Only this one is mine!
Drop even one... and you're dead!
R-Right...
I just said you're dead
if you drop even one!
I'm sorry! It wasn't on purpose!
You just have too many!
What are you going to do
if they're damaged?!
This is Fushiguro.
Yes.
Just go back and get another!
Yeah.
All right. See you.
What?
Gojo-sensei said to come.
Huh? Why?
A mission.
A top secret one.
What?
Didn't we just finish taking care of one?
Why not?
Gojo-sensei's saying it's top secret.
So it must be big.
He says that pretty often.
He says it all the time.
Yeah, but so what?
Let's go.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
To Be Continued